{
    "id": "01328a6ea02d48138bead4dd3281bd5a",
    "title": "Hear And Listen",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Did you .............................. a noise now?",
            "description": "To hear is to perceive something with the ear.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "885d51323da34bcfa9a38fd1d387e395"
        },
        {
            "question": "A large audience .................................. the concert last night.",
            "description": "We generally use hear to talk about experiencing the whole of a performance or speech.",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened",
                "listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "213fd42e895e4879a4523cb95dd841d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................. that you are moving to Switzerland.",
            "description": "Hear can mean be informed or be told.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba28b1d0a581424bbd28df76e035bfe9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't ................................. the doorbell.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "hear",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9bd240029de45eea75f9d44c126330f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I had ......................................... his advice.",
            "description": "To listen to something is to pay attention to it.",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened",
                "listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "02c2a454684d4d84b352297490184778"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge will ................................... the case next month.",
            "description": "To hear a case is to investigate it officially.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5da51aeb4a8d4e66a1c33177ea27898f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is important. Please .................................. carefully.",
            "description": "When there is no object, we use listen instead of listen to.",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "hear",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9efc678c32646758ffcc0e9f149d5f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you ................................. me properly?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "514456e5f7f146b9aadb1f4bc8af1df5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know what he said. I was not ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearing",
                "listening",
                "listening to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c40f7e4c8c444831b33acb5118309258"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................. someone knocking on the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened",
                "listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acaaaff09e304ecd9a5b10d55f8b9e87"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ………………………….. me. I am going to tell you something.",
            "description": "Before an object, we use listen to.",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "03144896824c4000882b612a7418ce7e"
        }
    ]
}